Martha Graham Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Photographic Material (Box 239-273)
  - Martha Graham with Others
    - Ford, Gerald and Betty (Box-folder 254/47, 266/4)
    - Halston; Minnelli; Peck, Gregory (Box-folder 255/3)
    - Halston; Tiegs, Cheryl; other (Box-folder 255/4)
    - Halston, others (Box-folder 255/5)
    - Hawkins (Box-folder 255/6)
    - Hawkins and others (Box-folder 255/7)
    - Hinkson (Box-folder 263/18)
    - Hinkson, Ross, Turney, and others (contact sheet) (Box-folder 255/8)
    - Horst, Louis (in Graham’s studio), 1938 (Box-folder 255/9)
    - Horst, others (in Graham’s studio), 1938 (Box-folder 255/10)
    - Kelly, Gene; Reagan, Nancy; and others (Box-folder 255/11)
    - Legarda, Mrs. Trinidad (Box-folder 255/12)
    - Minnelli (Box-folder 255/13)
    - Nureyev (Box-folder 255/14)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, and others at rehearsal (Box-folder 255/15)
    - Protas, Ron (Box-folder 255/16)
    - Malagueña with Ted Shawn, 1922 (Box-folder 255/17)
    - Sargent, Georgia (sister) (Box-folder 255/1-2)
    - Sills, Beverly (Box-folder 266/3)
    - St. Denis, Ruth (Box-folder 255/18)
    - Taj Mahal (Box-folder 263/16)
    - White House, 1976 (Box-folder 263/17)
    - White House, 1976 Metal of Freedom (Box-folder 266/5)
    - Yuriko and students in rehearsal (Box-folder 255/19)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 255/20)
    - Unidentified groups (Box-folder 263/15)
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 263/14)
    - Unidentified contact sheets (Box-folder 255/21)
    - Unidentified negatives and slides (Box-folder 255/22)
  - Family Members with Graham
    - Aunt Ree, father, Georgia (sister), Lizzie (Elizabeth Prendergast), Mary (sister), uncle; Aunt Ree, Georgia, Lizzie, Mary, mother, uncle (Box-folder 254/37)
    - Georgia, Mary (Box-folder 254/38)
    - Georgia, Mary, mother (Box-folder 254/39)
    - Georgia, Mary, William (brother) (Box-folder 254/40)
    - Mary (Box-folder 254/41)
    - Mary, mother (Box-folder 254/42)
    - Mother (Box-folder 254/43)
    - Miscellaneous family (Box-folder 254/44)
  - Family Members (no Graham)
    - Aunt Ree (Box-folder 256/13)
    - [Aunt Ree], mother (Box-folder 256/14)
    - Father (George Greenfield Graham) (Box-folder 256/15)
    - Georgia (Box-folder 256/16)
    - Georgia, Lizzie (Elizabeth Prendergast), Mary (Box-folder 256/17)
    - Georgia, Mary, William (Box-folder 256/18)
    - Georgia, mother (Box-folder 256/19)
    - Grandmother, great-grandmother (Box-folder 256/20)
    - Grandmother, mother, others (Box-folder 256/21)
    - Mary (Box-folder 256/22)
    - Mother (Jane Beers Graham) (Box-folder 256/23)
    - Parents; parents with children; unidentified large group (Box-folder 256/24)
    - William (Box-folder 256/25)
    - Miscellaneous family members (Box-folder 256/26)
  - Special Events and Tours (Graham with others)
    - Bloomingdale’s event (contact sheet), 1981 (Box-folder 255/23)
    - Family of Man Awards dinner, 1968 (Box-folder 255/24)
    - Berlin, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 255/25)
    - India, 1950s (Box-folder 255/26)
    - Indonesia, 1955 (Box-folder 255/27)
    - Lecture/demonstration in Cologne, Germany, 1962 (Box-folder 255/29)
    - Lecture/demonstration at Lincoln Center (Box-folder 255/30)
    - Martha Graham Center (contact sheets), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 255/31)
    - Philippines (Box-folder 255/32)
    - Portugal (Box-folder 255/33)
    - Rehearsal for Primitive Mysteries (Horst, MG, dancers, dog), 1931 (Box-folder 255/34)
    - Rehearsal for Primitive Mysteries (Yuriko, Hodes [Linda]), 1982 (Box-folder 255/35)
    - Rehearsal for Rite of Spring, 1984 (Box-folder 255/36)
    - Taiwan (Box-folder 255/37)
    - White House (Gerald and Betty Ford and others) (Box-folder 255/38)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 255/39)
  - Other People/Places (no Graham)
    - Alvarez, Anita (Box-folder 256/1)
    - Asakawa, Takako at Carnegie Hall; Asakawa, Takako at the New York World’s Fair, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 256/2)
    - Bird, Bonnie (Box-folder 256/3)
    - Bird, Dorothy (Box-folder 256/4)
    - Butler, John and other (Bennington College) (Box-folder 256/5)
    - Chase, David (contact sheet) (Box-folder 256/6)
    - Copland, Aaron (Box-folder 256/7)
    - Cunningham, Merce (technique demonstration) (Box-folder 256/8)
    - De Valois, Ninette, 1961 (Box-folder 256/9)
    - Denishawn Company (Box-folder 256/10)
    - Dietrich, Marlene (postcard) (Box-folder 256/11)
    - Duncan, Isadora (Box-folder 256/12)
    - Gutelius, Phyllis (Box-folder 256/27)
    - Halston (Box-folder 256/28)
    - Hawkins (Box-folder 256/29)
    - Hinkson, Mary (Box-folder 256/30)
    - Horst (Box-folder 256/31)
    - Horst, St. Denis (Box-folder 256/32)
    - Horst, others (Box-folder 256/33)
    - Kinch, Myra (Box-folder 256/34)
    - Lyman, Peggy (Box-folder 256/35)
    - MacDonald, Betty; Sabin, Evelyn (Box-folder 256/36)
    - Martha Graham School of Contemporary Dance (Box-folder 264/2)
    - McDonald, Gene (Box-folder 264/3)
    - McGehee, Helen (Box-folder 264/4)
    - McGehee, Helen; Ross, Bertram (Box-folder 256/37)
    - Minnelli, Liza (Box-folder 256/38)
    - Minnelli, Liza; Peck, Gregory (Box-folder 256/39)
    - Native American (Box-folder 256/40)
    - Nureyev, Rudolf (Box-folder 264/1)
    - O’Donnell, May (Bennington College), 1938 (Box-folder 256/41)
    - Powell, Lillian and other in Julnar of the Sea (Box-folder 264/5)
    - Powell, Robert (Box-folder 256/42)
    - Protas, Ron (Box-folder 256/43)
    - Repertory Playhouse Associates (Box-folder 256/44)
    - Ross, Bertram (Box-folder 256/45)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box-folder 264/6)
    - Ross, Bertram (Box-folder 264/7)
    - (?) de Rothschild (Box-folder 264/8)
    - Shawn, Ted (Box-folder 264/9, 256/47)
    - Shawn, Ted and Ruth St. Denis (Box-folder 264/10)
    - Shawn and St. Denis in Jonas of the Sea (Box-folder 256/48)
    - Sherman, Maxine in The Incense (Box-folder 256/49)
    - Sparling, Peter (Box-folder 256/50)
    - St. Denis (Box-folder 256/51)
    - Swanson, Gloria and her husband (Box-folder 256/52)
    - Thompson, Clive (Box-folder 256/53)
    - Tully, Alice and other (Box-folder 256/54)
    - Turney, Matt (Box-folder 256/55)
    - Turney, Matt (Box-folder 264/11-12)
    - Weiss, Jerome (Box-folder 256/56)
    - Winter, Ethel (Box-folder 264/13)
    - Wood, David (Box-folder 264/14)
    - Yuriko (Box-folder 264/15, 256/57)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 264/16-20)
    - White House performance (Box-folder 264/21)
    - Rome (sculpture) (Box-folder 264/22)
    - Statues (Box-folder 264/23)
    - Temple of Dundar (Box-folder 264/24)
    - Woodpile (Box-folder 264/25)
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 256/46)
  - Miscellaneous and Unidentified Photographs
    - Bennington College (Box-folder 257/1)
    - China (Denishawn tour) (Box-folder 257/2)
    - Carnegie Hall, 1989 (Box-folder 257/3)
    - Israel (en route) (Box-folder 257/4)
    - Malaysia (Hodes and others) (Box-folder 257/5)
    - Mexico (Box-folder 257/6)
    - Technique demonstration (Box-folder 257/7)
    - Annual June course, 1945 (Box-folder 257/8)
    - Artwork of P Chann (Box-folder 257/9)
    - Cover of November 1950 The Atlantic (Box-folder 257/10)
    - Car accident, 1977 (Box-folder 257/11)
    - Doves (Box-folder 257/12)
    - Graham's home in Santa Barbara (Box-folder 257/13)
    - Louis Horst Memorial Chair, Jacob’s Pillow (Box-folder 257/14)
    - Martha Graham Center of Contemporary Dance (Box-folder 257/15)
    - Noguchi sets and models (Box-folder 257/16)
    - Spanish mission church (Box-folder 257/17)
    - Temple of Dundar (Metropolitan Museum of Art) (Box-folder 257/18)
    - White Sands National Monument (Box-folder 257/19)
    - Winter Garden, World Financial Center, 1989 (Box-folder 257/20)
    - Unidentified individuals (Box-folder 257/21)
    - Unidentified groups of people (Box-folder 257/22)
    - Unidentified contact sheets (Box-folder 257/23)
    - Unidentified negatives (Box-folder 257/24)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 257/25)
  - Photographs by Arnold Weissberger, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 267/1-3)
    - MG (alone); Performances (miscellaneous); Frontier (Box-folder 267/1)
    - Photographs by Arnold Weissberger, Rehearsal shots (miscellaneous), 1974 (Box-folder 267/2)
      - Lamentations (Box-folder 267/2)
      - “Pas de Deux” from White Swan (Box-folder 267/2)
      - Seraphic Dialogue (Box-folder 267/2)
      - Adorations (Box-folder 267/2)
    - Photographs by Arnold Weissberger, Performance shots, 1974 (Box-folder 267/3)
      - Night Journey (Box-folder 267/3)
      - Letter to the World (Box-folder 267/3)
      - Diversion of Angels (Box-folder 267/3)
      - Lucifer (Box-folder 267/3)
  - Photographs by Arnold Weissberger, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 267/4)
    - MG, Paul Newman, Betty Ford MG and Andy Warhol MG and Douglas Fairbanks, Jr. MG and Betty Ford MG, Mrs. Igor Stravinsky, and others MG and others (Box-folder 267/4)
  - Photographs by Arnold Weissberger (Box 273)
    - Album #9, 1972 Album #10, 1975 Album #11, 1976 Album #12, 1980 (Box 273)
  - Photo Album from Carroll Russell (Box 268)
  - Album #1: Far East trip (dinner party at the Rice Bowl) Album #2: Far East trip (dinner party at the Rice Bowl) (Box 269)
  - Album #3: Far East trip Album #4: Indonesia (Indonesian dance poses) (Box 270)
  - Album #5: Iran tour Album #6: Rubin Academy, Israel (Box 271)
  - Album #7: Family album Album #8: Georgia Graham and friends (Box 272)
- Clippings (Box 218-223)
  The Clippings series contains newspaper and other periodical reviews and articles about Martha Graham and the Martha Graham Dance Company, ranging from 1925 to 1996. A more extensive collection of reviews is contained in the Scrapbooks series.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1925; 1931; 1932; 1938 (Box-folder 218/1)
  - 1940; 1941; 1942; 1946 (Box-folder 218/2)
  - 1947 (Box-folder 218/3-4)
  - 1950; 1951; 1952; 1953 (Box-folder 218/5)
  - 1954; 1955 (Box-folder 218/6)
  - 1956; 1957; 1958 (Box-folder 218/7)
  - 1959; 1950s (n.d.) (Box-folder 218/8)
  - 1960; 1961; 1962 (Box-folder 219/1)
  - 1963; 1964; 1965; 1966 (Box-folder 219/2)
  - 1967; 1968 (Box-folder 219/3)
  - 1969 (Box-folder 219/4)
  - 1970 (Box-folder 219/5-7)
  - 1973 (Box-folder 220/1)
  - 1974 (Box-folder 220/2)
  - 1975 (Box-folder 220/3)
  - 1976 (Box-folder 220/4)
  - 1977 (Box-folder 220/5)
  - 1978 (Box-folder 220/6)
  - 1979 (Box-folder 220/7)
  - 1970s (n.d.) (Box-folder 220/8)
  - 1980; 1981 (Box-folder 221/1)
  - 1982; 1983 (Box-folder 221/2)
  - 1984; 1985 (Box-folder 221/3)
  - 1986 (Box-folder 221/4-5)
  - 1987 (Box-folder 222/1)
  - 1988 (Box-folder 222/2)
  - 1989; 1990 (Box-folder 222/3)
  - 1991 (Box-folder 222/4)
  - 1992 (Box-folder 222/5)
  - 1994; 1996 (Box-folder 222/6)
  - pre-1990s (n.d.) (Box-folder 223/1)
  - 1990s (n.d.) (Box-folder 223/2)
  - 1990s (n.d.) (Box-folder 223/3)
- Public Relations, Fundraising, and Special Events (Box 205-217)
  The Public Relations, Fundraising, and Special Events series consists of sponsor lists, potential donors, information on corporate and foundation solicitations, press releases, business plans, general public relations materials, grant proposals, and correspondence relating to the 1966 fundraising campaign. This series also contains flyers and posters dating from the 1920s to the 1990s as well as information on special events, galas, and benefits. The materials span 1947 to 1996.
  - 1947; 1950; 1960; 1971 (Box-folder 205/1)
  - 1972; 1973 (Box-folder 205/2)
  - 1975 (Box-folder 205/3)
  - 1984; 1986 (Box-folder 205/4)
  - 1987 (Box-folder 205/5)
  - 1987 journal ads (Box-folder 205/6)
  - 1987 journal ads (contracts) (Box-folder 205/7)
  - 1987-1988 fundraising report (Box-folder 205/8)
  - 1988 (Box-folder 205/9)
  - 1988 business plan (Box-folder 205/10)
  - 1988 guild membership campaign (Box-folder 205/11)
  - 1989 business plan (Box-folder 206/1)
  - 1989; 1990; 1991 (Box-folder 206/2)
  - 1992; 1993; 1995; 1996 (Box-folder 206/3)
  - Potential donors, directors, and advisory council members (Box-folder 206/4)
  - Plan for Martha Graham dancewear (Box-folder 206/5)
  - Staff/artist biographies; notes on repertory (Box-folder 206/6)
  - Program for the future (Box-folder 206/7)
  - Plan for debt reduction, undated (Box-folder 206/8)
  - Martha Graham Dance, undated (Box-folder 206/9)
  - Grant Proposals and Letters of Inquiry (Box 207-209)
    - Jerome Foundation, 1979 Doris Duke Foundation, 1988 Liz Claiborne Foundation, 1988 Wang Machines, 1988 ABC Television Network, 1989 American Tobacco Co., 1989 American Airlines, 1989 Chase Manhattan Bank, 1989 Helena Rubinstein Foundation, 1989 Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1989 SER, 1989 AT&T Foundation, 1990 Chase Manhattan Bank, 1990 Cosmair, Inc., 1990 Crédit Agricole, 1990 Crum and Forster Foundation, 1990 Equitable Life Assurance Society of the U.S., 1990 Educational Foundation of America, 1991 EPAC, Inc., 1991 (Box-folder 207/1)
    - Cowles Charitable Trust ELF Atochem North America, 1994 New York Community Trust, 1994 Owen Cheatham Foundation, 1994 Booth Ferris Foundation, 1995-1996(?) Hecksher Foundation for Children, 1995 (Box-folder 207/2)
    - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1995 Metropolitan Life Foundation, 1995 National Initiative to Preserve American Dance, 1995 Heathcote Art Foundation, 1995 (Box-folder 207/3)
    - Coca Cola Company, 1996 (Box-folder 207/4)
    - Coca Cola Company, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 207/5)
    - Graham Next, 1994 A Chance to Dance (Lincoln Center), 1995 (Box-folder 207/6)
    - Fund for Dance, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 207/7)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1989 (Box-folder 207/8)
    - Educational outreach programs funding, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 207/9)
    - New York State Council on the Arts applications, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 208/1)
    - New York State Council on the Arts applications, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 208/2)
    - National Endowment for the Arts application, 1973 (Box-folder 208/3)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, challenge grant, 1983 (Box-folder 208/4)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, challenge grant, 1983 (Box-folder 208/5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1987 (Box-folder 208/6)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1988 (Box-folder 208/7)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, final report, 1989 (Box-folder 208/8)
    - 1966 Fundraising Campaign (Box-folder 209/1)
    - 1966 Fundraising Campaign (Box-folder 209/2)
    - 1966 Fundraising Campaign (Box-folder 209/3)
    - 1966 Fundraising Campaign (Box-folder 209/4)
    - 1966 Fundraising Campaign (Box-folder 209/5)
    - Undated or unidentified (Box-folder 209/6)
    - School-related materials (Box-folder 209/7)
    - Lists/Public relations (Box-folder 209/8)
    - Film projects (Box-folder 209/9)
    - Film projects (Box-folder 209/10)
    - Film projects (Box-folder 209/11)
    - Miro lithograph fundraising project, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 209/12)
  - Public Relations (Box 209-211)
    - Warhol purchases, 1987 (Box-folder 209/13)
    - Flyers and posters, 1920s; 1930s; 1940s; 1950s (Box-folder 210/1)
    - Flyers and posters, 1960s (Box-folder 210/2)
    - Flyers and posters, 1970s; 1983; 1984; 1985 (Box-folder 211/1)
    - Flyers and posters, 1986; 1987; 1988 (Box-folder 211/2)
    - Flyers and posters, 1988; 1989 (Box-folder 211/3)
    - Flyers and posters, 1990s (Box-folder 211/4)
    - Flyers and posters, undated (Box-folder 211/5)
    - Flyers and posters: non-Graham (Box-folder 211/6)
  - Special Events (Box 211-217)
    - Tribute to Martha Graham, 1974 (Box-folder 211/7)
    - 50th anniversary season, 1975 (Box-folder 211/8)
    - Celebration tribute to Alexander Calder, 1977 (Box-folder 211/9)
    - Opening night at the Metropolitan Opera House, 1978 (Box-folder 211/10)
    - A celebration for Halston, 1979 (Box-folder 211/11)
    - 55th anniversary season, 1980 (Box-folder 211/12)
    - Gala world premiere, Washington, D.C., 1981 “A Halston Night for Martha Graham,” 1981 (Box-folder 211/13)
    - Martha Graham Guild gala garden party, 1982 (Box-folder 211/14)
    - Soiree de Gala, 1984 (Box-folder 211/15)
    - February tribute year, 1984 (Box-folder 211/16)
    - Los Angeles tribute to Martha Graham, 1984 (Box-folder 211/17)
    - Martha Graham School gala, 1984 (Box-folder 211/18)
    - World premiere gala, 1985 “A Supper on the Côte d’Azur,” 1985 (Box-folder 211/19)
    - 60th anniversary celebration, Philadelphia, 1986 (Box-folder 212/1)
    - 60th anniversary diamond jubilee, 1986 (Box-folder 212/2)
    - 60th anniversary diamond jubilee, 1986 (Box-folder 212/3)
    - 60th anniversary diamond jubilee, 1986 (Box-folder 212/4)
    - “Temptations of the Moon,” 1986 (Box-folder 212/5)
    - “Temptations of the Moon,” 1986 (Box-folder 212/6)
    - “Temptations of the Moon,” 1986 (Box-folder 212/7)
    - “Peggy Sue Got Married,” 1986 (Box-folder 212/8)
    - “Peggy Sue Got Married,” 1986 (Box-folder 212/9)
    - Cake sale gala, 1987 (Box-folder 212/10)
    - Cake sale gala, 1987 (Box-folder 212/11)
    - Cake sale gala, 1987 (Box-folder 212/12)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/1)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/2)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/3)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/4)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/5)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/6)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/7)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/8)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/9)
    - New York City season gala, 1987 (Box-folder 213/10)
    - “A Diamond for Martha,” 1987 (Box-folder 214/1)
    - “A Diamond for Martha,” 1987 (Box-folder 214/2)
    - Cake sale, 1987 (Box-folder 214/3)
    - New York City season gala, 1988 (Box-folder 214/4)
    - New York City season gala, 1988 (Box-folder 214/5)
    - New York City season gala, 1988 (Box-folder 214/6)
    - New York City season gala, 1988 (Box-folder 214/7)
    - New York City season gala, 1988 (Box-folder 214/8)
    - New York City season gala, 1988 (Box-folder 214/9)
    - New York City season gala, 1988 (Box-folder 214/10)
    - Night journey harbor cruise, 1988 (Box-folder 214/11)
    - Open rehearsal, 1988 (Box-folder 214/12)
    - Special evening for the Gotham Chapter of YPO, 1988 (Box-folder 214/13)
    - “In the American Grain” gala, 1989 (Box-folder 215/1)
    - “American Document” gala, 1989 (Box-folder 215/2)
    - Night journey harbor cruise, 1989 (Box-folder 215/3)
    - Suzanne Vega/Philip Glass benefit, 1989 (Box-folder 215/4)
    - Boston gala, 1989 (Box-folder 215/5)
    - Cake sale, 1989 (Box-folder 215/6)
    - Homage to Martha (Sotheby’s), 1989 (Box-folder 215/7)
    - 96th birthday celebration, 1990 (Box-folder 215/8)
    - 96th birthday celebration, 1990 (Box-folder 215/9)
    - 64th anniversary gala, 1990 (Box-folder 215/10)
    - 64th anniversary gala, 1990 (Box-folder 215/11)
    - 64th anniversary gala, 1990 (Box-folder 215/12)
    - “A Valentine for Martha” (Box-folder 215/13)
    - “A Valentine for Martha” (Box-folder 215/14)
    - Celebration of the publication of Blood Memory, 1991 (Box-folder 215/15)
    - 66th anniversary gala, 1992 (Box-folder 216/1)
    - 66th anniversary gala, 1992 (Box-folder 216/2)
    - 66th anniversary gala, 1992 (Box-folder 216/3)
    - 66th anniversary gala, 1992 (Box-folder 216/4)
    - 66th anniversary gala, 1992 (Box-folder 216/5)
    - 66th anniversary gala, 1992 (Box-folder 216/6)
    - “Champagne on Ice,” 1992 (Box-folder 216/7)
    - Harbor cruise, 1992 (Box-folder 216/8)
    - “Kick-Off-Your-Shoes,” 1993 (Box-folder 217/1)
    - 67th anniversary gala, 1993 (Box-folder 217/2)
    - 67th anniversary gala, 1993 (Box-folder 217/3)
    - 67th anniversary gala, 1993 (Box-folder 217/4)
    - “Radical Graham,” 1994 (Box-folder 217/5)
    - Centennial celebration, 1994 (Box-folder 217/6)
    - New York City season gala, 1995 (Box-folder 217/7)
- New York City Seasons and National and International Tours, 1948-1996 (Box 198-200)
  The New York City Seasons and National and International Tours series consists of correspondence, memoranda, telefaxes, telegrams, cast lists, budgets, and itineraries for the Graham Company’s New York City seasons and national and international tours between 1948 and 1996. Further information on the New York City seasons and touring can be found in Correspondence; Scrapbooks; Production Elements; and Public Relations, Fundraising, and Special Events.
  - 1948; 1949 (Box-folder 198/1)
  - 1950 (Box-folder 198/2)
  - 1955 (Box-folder 198/3)
  - 1962 (Box-folder 198/4)
  - 1963 (Box-folder 198/5)
  - 1967 (Box-folder 198/6)
  - 1970 (Box-folder 198/7)
  - 1971 (Box-folder 198/8)
  - 1972 (Box-folder 198/9)
  - 1973 (Box-folder 198/10)
  - 1974 (Box-folder 198/11)
  - 1974 (Box-folder 198/12)
  - 1974 Asia tour (Box-folder 198/13)
  - 1974 Asia tour (Box-folder 198/14)
  - 1974 Asia tour (Box-folder 198/15)
  - 1974 Asia tour (Box-folder 198/16)
  - 1975 (Box-folder 198/17)
  - 1980 (Box-folder 198/18)
  - 1983 (Box-folder 198/19)
  - 1984 (Box-folder 199/1)
  - 1985 (Box-folder 199/2)
  - 1986 (Box-folder 199/3)
  - 1987 (Box-folder 199/4)
  - 1988 (Box-folder 199/5)
  - 1988 (Box-folder 199/6)
  - 1989 (Box-folder 199/7)
  - 1989-1990 Asia tour (Box-folder 199/8)
  - 1989-1990 Asia tour (Box-folder 199/9)
  - 1989-1990 Asia tour (Box-folder 199/10)
  - 1990 (Box-folder 200/1)
  - 1991 (Box-folder 200/2)
  - 1992 (Box-folder 200/3)
  - 1993 (Box-folder 200/4)
  - 1994 (Box-folder 200/5)
  - 1995 (Box-folder 200/6)
  - 1996 Australia tour (Box-folder 200/7)
  - Undated cast and repertory lists (Box-folder 200/8)
  - Tour contact sheets (Box-folder 200/9)
  - Requirements list for tours, undated (Box-folder 200/10)
  - Undated or unidentified (Box-folder 200/11)
- Choreographic Notebooks (Box 274-275)
  The Choreographic Notebooks series contains notebooks of ideas, sketches, steps, and steps sequences for approximately twenty-three of Graham’s choreographic works. Many were published in 1973 as The Notebooks of Martha Graham, with an introduction by Nancy Wilson Ross and published by Harcourt Brace Jovanovich. The piano-rehearsal scores found in the Music Inventory series often contain choreographic notes.
  - In the End is My Beginning (Mary Queen of Scots) (Box-folder 274/1)
  - I Salute My Love (Box-folder 274/2)
  - Clytemnestra; Canticle for Innocent Comedians (Box-folder 274/3)
  - Heloise; Time of Snow (Later thoughts on Heloise and Abelard) (Box-folder 274/4)
  - Witch of Endor and Circe (Box-folder 274/5)
  - Notes for dances never choreographed (Box-folder 274/6)
  - Choreographic studies for Clytemnestra and Alcestis (Box-folder 274/7)
  - The Dark Meadow of the Soul (Box-folder 274/8)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Errand into the Maze) (Box-folder 274/9)
  - Studies for Saint Joan, Heloise and Abelard, and Phaedra (Box-folder 274/10)
  - Deaths and Entrances (Box-folder 274/11)
  - Every Soul is a Circus (Box-folder 275/1)
  - Medea (Cave of the Heart) (Box-folder 275/2)
  - Herodiade (Box-folder 275/3)
  - Panorama and Formal Dance (Box-folder 275/4)
  - Judith (Box-folder 275/5)
  - Unidentified (Box-folder 275/6)
  - Unidentified (Box-folder 275/7)
  - American Document (Box-folder 275/8)
  - Hecuba (Cortege of Eagles) (Box-folder 275/9)
- Correspondence (Box 229-238; 377-387; 398)